{
	"response_code": 0,
	"results": [{
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "Rate your overall Hackathon Experience",
			"correct_answer": "Excellent",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Good",
				"Fair",
				"Poor"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "open",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "What is your name?"
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "This is your first hackathon?",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "How organized did you feel this Hackathon was?",
			"correct_answer": "Very well organized!",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Very good, but could have been better",
				"It was ok",
				"Terrible. Just terrible."
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "open",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "What was your favorite aspect of the hackathon?"
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "The key to a loving and caring relationship is:",
			"correct_answer": "Sean Nakamura",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Communication",
				"Caring",
				"Practice"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "How would you rate the food?",
			"correct_answer": "Amazing. How did you accomplish this?",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Pretty good, but youâ€™re not going to win any awards",
				"Better than my cooking",
				"YOU POISONED ME!"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "The correct definition of DevOps is:",
			"correct_answer": "Jon Borgonia",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"An enterprise software development phrase used to mean a type of agile relationship between Development and IT Operations",
				"Something to do with deployments",
				"A process to improve relationships by advocating better communication and collaboration between the business units."
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What would motivate you the most?",
			"correct_answer": "Cash",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Software prizes",
				"3D printed trophies",
				"Pizza"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "How far would you travel for a Hackathon if first place was $5,000?",
			"correct_answer": "30+ miles",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"10-29 miles",
				"1-9 miles",
				"Walking distance"
			]
		},  {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What best describes you?",
			"correct_answer": "Professional",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Hacker",
				"College",
				"High School",
				"Anarchist"
			]
		},  {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "open",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "Why did you decide to attend this hackathon?"
		},  {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "How far would you travel for a Hackathon if first place was $5,000?",
			"correct_answer": "30+ miles",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"10-29 miles",
				"1-9 miles",
				"Walking distance"
			]
		},  {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What did you accomplish at this hackathon?",
			"correct_answer": "Time Travel",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Nothing",
				"Mayhem",
				"Scientific Discovery"
			]
		},  {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What Rick and Morty do you most identify with?",
			"correct_answer": "Rick",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Morty",
				"Beth",
				"Jerry",
				"Summer"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the best DNA source to encourage human mating via serum?",
			"correct_answer": "Vole",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Mantis",
				"Koala",
				"Rattlesnake"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "If you were to provide this Hackathon a spirit animal it would be:",
			"correct_answer": "Gorilla",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Kangaroo",
				"Komodo Dragon",
				"Lemur"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is best in life?",
			"correct_answer": "To crush your enemies",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"See them driven before you",
				"Hear the lamentation of their women",
				"Cheetos"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "You are stranded on a deserted island with your hackathon team. Who do you eat first?",
			"correct_answer": "Tenga",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Caity",
				"Matt",
				"Gina",
				"Jay",
				"Estefania",
				"Joe",
				"Marifel",
				"Lisa",
				"Nick",
				"Alex",
				"Nakaz"

			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "There are two types of people in the world. What are they?",
			"correct_answer": "Those that think Rick and Morty is the greatest show that has ever aired, and those who have not seen it.",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Those that view the glass as half full, and those that view the glass as half empty",
				"Apple users and those that are wrong",
				"Android users and those that are wrong"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the leading programming language in the world?",
			"correct_answer": "Profanity",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Python",
				"Javascript",
				"Ruby",
				"Java"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the best front end framework?",
			"correct_answer": "RBveaJS",
			"incorrect_answers":[
				"ReactJS",
				"Angular2",
				"ViewJS"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "How old is Joe Karlsson?",
			"correct_answer": "He is immortal and has existed before and after the construct of what we call time", 
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"35",
				"41",
				"24"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "Ray Farias is secretly",
			"correct_answer": "A magical pug that can transform into a human with pug-like qualities", 
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"A guitarist",
				"A bassist",
				"A Developer"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "Within Jason Sewell's beard lies ancient secrets. Explore this beard and you will find:",
			"correct_answer": "A mini Jason Sewell with another mystical beard" , 
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"The Borgonias",
				"The secrets of Dev League",
				"Fantasty Little League"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "open",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "How the fuck did you get this far in this survey?" 
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "Who wears short shorts?",
			"correct_answer": "Jonathan Tan" , 
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"I wear short shorts",
				"Elves",
				"Slackbot"
			]
		}, {
			"category": "Hackathon",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the correct response when being confront with a difficult coding challenge?",
			"correct_answer": "WHAT YOU FAKA" , 
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"FAKA WHAT",
				"DIS FAKA?",
				"Further inquiry required"
			]
		}
]
}